imusiciandigital.com 2014-12-10

# Privacy Policy - iMusician Digital

### Principal

The safety and privacy of personal data has a special value for iMusician Digital AG (hereinafter iMusician Digital). The collection, processing and usage of personal data shall only be undertaken with the consent of the individual or due to a legal obligation. Should anonymous or pseudonymous data be needed for business purposes, then only these forms of data shall be used.

Personal data stored at iMusician Digital is protected by extensive technical and operational safeguards against potential unauthorised access or abuse. Our security procedures are regularly reviewed along with the latest technological developments.

### iMusician Digital Orders and Membership

We collect; store; modify; use and transmit personal data for their own specific purposes towards the justification and settlement of the user’s contract or contract relationships, including individual and personal customer advice and support, and to protect the legitimate business interests of iMusician Digital. When necessary, we will transmit personal data to third parties (such as delivery companies). Only information that is needed to carry out its task will be transmitted and used.

The usage and transmission of personal data for advertising and market-research purposes is permitted by iMusician Digital, unless the user asks us to withhold their personal information when setting up their contract with us. Users can opt-out of the usage of their data at any time within their iMusician Digital user-account or by sending a request via email to music@iMusicianDigital.com

The usage of personal data for other appropriate purposes is dependent on prior consent from the user.

If a user agrees to the forwarding of newsletters from a shop owner, then they will receive the newsletter content via iMusician Digital. The shop owner sends the newsletter information to iMusician Digital and a transmission of the users personal data to the shop-owner does not take place.

### Usage of iMusician Digital’s Online Offers

iMusician Digital collects and uses personal user data due to legal obligations or when permission from a user is given, for the reason of content-wise alterations or changes to the contractual relations with the user in terms of the usage of tele-media.

As far as is necessary, iMusician Digital collects and uses a personal data in order to enable users to operate their online service; for accounting; further legally permissible cases or with the users consent.

iMusician Digital collects and uses data contained in log-files that the user’s internet browser transmits to us. The data we receive is the user’s browser type/version; operating system; referring URLs (the user’s previously visited site); hostname (IP address) of the accessing computer and the time of server inquiry. In order to ensure the safe communication of the iMusician Digital online service – it is not necessary for iMusician Digital to use the data collected in connection with the specific user. Therefore, after statistical evaluation the data will be deleted and not used in connection with the user.

### Usage of Cookies

For the reason of improving iMusician Digital’s online service, the commonly-named system of ‘Cookies’ are used. Cookies are text files, which are stored on a users computer when they visit a website. Cookies are used either once or over a longer period of time to use a user’s recurring attitudes within the iMusician Digital site to their benefit – in terms of personalising the iMusician Digital online experience and its functions and tools towards individual user’s needs. The text files contain no address data (i.e. user’s names and E-Mail data) or other personal information. iMusician Digital will not link data found in these text files with other data sources. Cookies serve to further our analysis of web-page usage and enables us to make our service more user-friendly; more effective and safer.

### Deactivation of Cookies

Users can set their web browser to halt the storage of the data files known as Cookies. In some cases this can lead to certain services and website functions to become unusable.

### User Rights to Access to Personal Information

Visitors and users of iMusician Digital’s web page can request (free of charge) access to any information held about them and its origin; any recipients of their data and the reason for the storage of such data.

### Google Advertising

We have implemented and use Google Display Advertising, more specifically remarketing, to advertise online. Third-party vendors including Google, show our ads on sites across theiInternet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, usefirst-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-partycookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for DisplayAdvertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the AdsPreferences Manager.
